<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>CJ Psychos</name>
  <packageId>Crackajack.CJPsychos</packageId>
  <author>Crackajack</author>
  <url></url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.3</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>erdelf.HumanoidAlienRaces</packageId>
      <displayName>Humanoid Alien Races</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/839005762</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/erdelf/AlienRaces/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>erdelf.HumanoidAlienRaces</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <description>
  [h1]Ready to ruin your day.[/h1]
  
  [i]Have you ever fought in a very important and terrible war for 200 years,
  woke up from cryptosleep after setting out for the next system to conquer,
  just to find out you slept through the end and have been forgotten?[/i]
  [b]No? Well, then its no miracle these people feel misunderstood.[/b]
  
  As everybody paying rough attention to galactic history knows, there have been countless of wars across countless of systems, some of them still raging today. 
  As a byproduct of this, some valued soldiers have been kept around for long times.
  their livespans artificially elongated, healed and resurrected many times to do the one job at which they excel: Killing.
  While modern war shrinks speak of the "post traumatic war addiction syndrome", the regular soldiers often refer to them as "goddamn psychos", especially after witnessing one at work.
  While varying individually, patients are reported to vent their anger by fighting, lighting fires, consuming any kind of drugs and general antisocial behavior.
  Above all else though, they enjoy violence. To be good at your job, you have to like it, they say.
  
  [u]Psychos will show up in raids, and with allies.[/u]
  They are very effective on the battlefield, and love drugs. Seriously, they´re dangerous and fked in the head.
  
  [b]Not crazy op, but beware.[/b]
  
  
  Will look like garbage, you need to deactivate texture compression, use HD pawn rendering, or the texture compression setting from VE Framework
  
  XML: Three Legged Wolf, "Art": CrackaJack 
  
</description>
</ModMetaData>

